<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE reference PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Reference//EN" "reference.dtd">
<reference xml:lang="en-US" id="r_sicherheitshinweise">
	<title>General safety guidelines</title>
	<refbody>
		<section>
			<note type="caution">Labelling regulations for all service water lines with "NOT POTABLE WATER"! apply e.g. an <keyword keyref="prod-series"/> labelling system.</note>
			<note type="important"><b>Potable Water Regulation (TrinkwV 2001) ยง 13 (3)</b>
				<q>The business owner and other owners of systems that are intended for obtaining or providing water that does not meet the quality of water for human consumption, and which
					are installed domestically in addition to the water supply systems as defined in ยง 3, No. 2, must present these systems to the competent authority at the moment of
					commissioning. If such systems are already being operated, notification must be submitted immediately</q> (see <xref href="../appendix/r_registration-installation.xml"
					format="dita"/>)</note>
			<note type="important"><b>Waste Water Regulation AbwV ยง 3 (2)</b>
				<q>Prior to the installation of an own recovery system, the customer must inform the water utility company. The customer must take the appropriate steps to ensure that the own
					system will not have any repercussions on the public water supply network</q> (see <xref href="../appendix/r_registration-water-utilities.xml" format="dita"/>)</note>
			<note type="restriction">Installation must be carried out by trained qualified staff.</note>
			<note type="caution">When carrying out the installation the current technical rules for domestic installations must be observed (<i>DIN1988</i>, <i>EN1717</i>).</note>
			<note type="caution">The system must be fitted with its own fuse protection (FI).</note>
			<note type="caution">The installation room must be provided with floor drainage.</note>
			<note type="caution">The grey water manifolds must be vented in such a way that the air blown into the wastewater system can escape freely via the vent of the grey water
				manifold.</note>
			<note>When operated correctly, the treated grey water will attain the quality stipulated in the <i>Bathing Water Directive of the EU</i>.</note>
			<note type="danger">The system must be <b>disconnected from the supply voltage</b> before performing any maintenance or repair work.</note>
			<note type="restriction">Emptying of the grey water vessel must only be carried out by trained service staff. If the filter dries out, this will destroy the membrane.</note>
			<note type="caution"><p><i>EN 12056-1</i> defines grey water as faecal-free, slightly contaminated wastewater, such as that accumulated from taking showers, or baths or from washing
					hands, and also that which comes out of the washing machine and can be used as service and process water when treated. A grey water treatment system is used exclusively
					for the treatment and recycling of slightly contaminated, faecal-free wastewater.</p>
				<p>Due to the fat content, a kitchen drain should not be connected.</p>
				<p>In the case of highly contaminated wastewater from toilets, kitchen drains or washing machines, quality objectives of treatment will not be achieved and damage to the
					membrane cannot be ruled out.</p>
				<p>The supply of strong alkaline cleaning products (chlorine cleaner etc.), dispersion paints, lacquers, hair dyes, oils and fats affects the performance of the membrane and
					the quality of the service water and must be avoided. Large amounts of fats and oils in particular can cause irreversible damage to the membrane.</p></note>
		</section>
	</refbody>
</reference>
